Mother is better now, Mayor.
And thanks again.
I know family emergencies
are never convenient.
[ZIPS]
But after some personal reflection,
I realized I have to be with her.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Everything I am started with her.
You sure you weren't followed?
- Yes.
- Good.
You've changed your appearance.
The suit is necessary.
The properties inside
of it help me continue
my acclimation process
when I'm outside the
reflection modulation chamber.
Now...
It's time to get rid of my husband.
We begin by dismantling
everything that protects him.
You know where to start.
Success is assured.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[EXCITING MUSIC]
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Guys, shouldn't it be all hands on desk
with Iris, Kamilla, and Singh
stuck in the Mirrorverse?
Hey, you're just as important.
Uh, Ms. Caitlin? Or Frost?
Uh, they're going to
the Arctic, not Ozz-fest.
How are you so bad at everything?
Caity keeps our heavy
coats in the back closet.
I'll check on it.
Right. That makes more sense.
You're so good at this kind of stuff...
so mad at me.
Little bit. Mm.
Nash, Allegra will
come around eventually.
You just have to be there when she does.
Trust the process.
Pretty wise for a popsicle.
Thanks. Got a Dib-ploma to prove it.
- [LAUGHS]
- Ba-dum-bum.
Uh... cool.
- Can I borrow this?
- Sure.
I'm really gonna miss you.
- Me too.
- Hmm?
[SOFT MUSIC]
I mean, all... we all are.
Aww. There's hope for you yet.
Enough. Okay.
You stay frosty.
♪ ♪
[ECHOLOCATION RINGING]
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
And honey, it's okay.
I promise you you can handle anything.
You just gotta remember.
She's your mom too.
Of course I am.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Hi, Killer Frost.
Uh...
it's just Frost now.
Hi.
Okay, um. [CLEARS THROAT]
We're gonna leave you two alone.
Give us a call when you
get settled in the north.
[WHIMPERS]
Give 'em hell.
[SIGHS] So...
I, um, I think I should run
a few tests before we leave.
Check your baseline for
any ribonucleic anomalies.
Great.
Eva's been missing for over 24 hours.
Where are we with facial recognition?
Satellites have turned up zilch.
The Artificial Speed
Force isn't finished yet,
so I still can't do my
usual sweeps of the city.
Right. Uh, why are we meeting here?
I have a backlog of cases.
I can't lose my CSI job
along with everything else.
A job...
[POIGNANT MUSIC]
Eva said that she had
unfinished business.
Is there any way that
she meant that literally?
Oh, if she wants to get McCulloch back,
she does have to deal with Black Hole.
So find Black Hole, find Eva.
- Mm-hmm.
- Any idea where to start?
Actually, no.
Maybe.
- Ralph.
- Where'd you get that?
- Sue gave it to me.
- She gave you that?
- She gave that to you?
- She gave that to me.
And it turns out that Black Hole's logo
is embedded inside.
Dude, there's serious UV
energy coming off that thing.
Can I?
Huh.
[ACTIVATES, WHIRRS]
Oh, yeah.
This is a Triangulation Cartograph.
It's a treasure map.
Allegra. Aim it over this.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
The center's at 42nd and Darby.
Hang on.
42nd and Darby...
- Holy heck.
- What?
Well, it turns out that
is a ginormous warehouse
with five subterranean levels.
Ralph and I will check it out.
You two take comms.
N... [SIGHS]
Let me just... excuse me.
♪ ♪
[BLOWING]
Could be a long night.
I made us a couple of coffees.
- I hate coffee.
- No coffee.
Guys, we're in.
All right. Be careful.
Place like that could
have a guard or two.
More like five.
They were all stabbed.
By a mirror-bayonet, I'm guessing.
[WHISTLES]
That is a lot of bad-guy stuff.
It's Black Hole's depository.
Sue said that Carver was
blackmailing her parents.
This is bank statements,
investment records.
This must be everything
that Carver has on them.
- I'm taking this.
- All right.
[LIQUID TRICKLING]
It smells like gasoline in here.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Singh.
I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
Tell that to those guards you killed.
They left me no choice.
I have to assure Eva's success.
Just put down the flare gun.
Help us bring Carver to justice.
[CHUCKLES]
Mother's not interested
in your brand of justice.
Singh. Singh!
This isn't you.
You still don't get it, do you?
[CRASH]
Carver was there that night.
[EXPLODES, MIRROR WHIRRING]
He let the mirror keep her.
He never tried to rescue her.
Instead, he sold her tech
to the highest bidder.
For weapons, blackmail, or worse.
And that is why Carver
is a dead man.
[FLAMES WHOOSHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Uh, not working.
[RADIO CRACKLING]
Guys?
Allen, Dibny, are you guys there?
Barely.
What do we do now?
The only thing we can.
Protect Carver.
♪ ♪
And our guy knows to destroy anything
that could tie me to the warehouse?
Yes, but there's
nothing left to destroy.
Everything we had was incinerated.
Replace the items.
Quickly and quietly.
Don't use The Three.
They can't know they're off leash.
If someone is coming after me,
I'll need their protection.
Hello. Officer Allen.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Please.
You're not here to slap me, are you?
[LAUGHS]
Captain West went for the left side.
How is he, by the way?
Look, there's no easy
way to say this, so...
Your wife wants to kill you.
But CCPD can't keep you safe.
My wife is dead.
Eva's been trapped in another dimension
for the last six years.
Place called the Mirrorverse.
But you already knew that.
If Eva did escape that
wretched place, I'd know.
This is about your wife, isn't it?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I came across this footage
from my wife's office
a couple of weeks ago.
You knew Iris was abducted?
Your wife was a problem.
Her disappearance was fortuitous.
What happened to my wife?
The same thing that happened to my Eva.
She's gone. They both are.
No.
There has to be a way to get her back.
I used to think that too.
But if Iris is still alive in there,
there's probably nothing
left of her to save.
I had the most brilliant minds
in the world study that...
Mirrorverse.
You know what they found?
It's incompatible with the human brain.
That place warps the mind
until the person is
no longer recognizable.
Your Iris
is long gone.
I suggest you accept that
and move on.
♪ ♪
Oh, so one more thing.
How do you know Eva's coming after me?
Who else would've burnt
down your warehouse?
42nd and Darby, right?
I'd never buy on that side of town.
And I don't need protecting.
Mm. [CHUCKLES]
You give Captain West my best.
Without the satellites,
finding Chief Singh feels impossible.
I know.
We'll have to go find him ourselves.
[SIGHS]
Every time I interact with this place,
the neural dissonance gets worse.
And what if Eva comes back?
Then what?
Look.
Things in this place may be backwards,
but everything works.
We just... we just
have to figure out how.
[NEURAL DISSONANCE RINGING]
[EXCLAIMING]
Did you see the map of the city?
You just said looking at
those was too dangerous.
No, I didn't mean to, but I was thinking
about finding David,
and the map came into view.
There... there was thermal energy
coming from a specific place.
I'm not sure where, but
that has to be David.
There was like a... a
radius, almost like a beacon.
I... I feel like if I could just focus,
I could... I can find his location.
No, Iris. Come on, look at you!
No, I'm acclimating
to this place, Kamilla.
That's why I can see
the map and you can't.
I can find David.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[KNOCKING]
- Mrs. Dearbon.
- Hi.
Mr. Dearbon, so great to see you again.
I have fantastic news.
- So it turns out that s...
- Oh.
So you are the person
that my parents employed to find me.
It's so good to meet you. [CHUCKLES]
[CHUCKLES] Hi.
And please forgive me.
I... I never meant to cause a stir.
I read "Eat, Pray, Love,"
and I took the pray part just
a little bit too seriously.
[CHUCKLES ANGRILY]
Our Susie joined a
mindfulness retreat in India.
I meant to stay for a month
and then lost track
of the weeks, months.
Oh, well.
Happens, right?
Mr. Dibny, while we're delighted
to have our Susie back,
we realize how much trouble you went to.
[LAUGHS] Do you have a pen?
Uh...
Oh, heck. Wouldn't you know?
I'm fresh out.
Let me just check that hallway closet.
Ms. Dearbon, could you
help me look for a pen?
- Of course.
- We'll be right back.
You need a legal pad or anything?
Why would you call my parents?
So that diamond that
you gave me, it turns out
that it has a map for
Black Hole's stash house.
- I did some recon.
- Ohh!
I thought breaking and entering
was a line Elongated Man didn't cross.
Will you... inside voices please.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Look.
Carver had files with
your parents names on them.
Those files contain the evidence
he was using to extort them.
What do you mean "had"?
Well... [LAUGHS]
Things got toasty,
and Carver's blackmail
arsenal got cooked.
You torched the place?
No. I... no.
Okay. How do I say this?
There's a Mirrorverse dimension.
There's these pod people running around.
They're claiming innocent lives.
It's very "Invasion of the
Bodies." You know what?
Why don't we just
forget about that part?
The point is your parents are safe.
Yeah. I already knew that.
Well, you're welcome. It
was really no... Wait. What?
Yeah, Carver called last week.
Said he had a change of heart.
Guys like Carver don't
have hearts to change.
Agreed.
But my parents are safe,
and I can finally go home.
I don't understand. If we agreed...
Enough, slick.
You really wanna help me?
Leave us in peace.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE] _
Did he say who wants
his head on a pike now?
[MIRROR SHIMMERING]
[SIGHS]
_
[MIRROR SHIMMERING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[PHOTON RIFLE ACTIVATES, WHIRRS]
Who's there?
Hello, Kimiyo.
Shall we do this the easy way...
Or the hard way?
[PHOTON RIFLE FIRES]
[GLASS SHIMMERS]
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
Sunshine?
♪ ♪
Hoshi?
Ultraviolet?
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I'm glad Carver turned you down.
After what he did to
my cousin, Joe, Iris,
he deserves what he gets.
He doesn't deserve to die.
What if he's telling the truth
about the Mirrorverse affecting minds?
Or he's lying.
He's not exactly the paragon of truth.
I don't think he's lying.
I think it could be neural dissonance.
I came across this Earth on my travels
where any visitor to that
Earth immediately suffers
a traumatic psychological state.
Neural dissonance.
This could be that.
I'm glad someone believes me.
I need your help after all, Allen.
Federal Protection.
The full Joe West treatment.
What happened to your killer minions?
Eva got to them first, didn't she?
You gonna help me or not?
[SCOFFS]
Look, get me into protection,
and Joe can get out of it.
One call from me
and he's sleeping in
his own bed tonight.
[SCOFFS] You're a real piece
of work. You know that?
That sounded like a yes to me.
[TABLET BEEPS]
Huh, that's interesting.
The stoichiometric ratio is manifesting
in a way that's abnormal.
[SIGHS]
It'd be so much easier
if Caitlin were here to help analyze.
I could help.
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry.
I just... I just meant that I could use
an expert in meta-DNA.
[SIGHS] I forgot.
I figured.
Probably because every
time you look at me,
you just see Thomas
and the monster he became.
You're not a monster.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
You protected Caitlin from
her father and then some,
which is a hell of a
lot more than I ever did.
You know, to be honest,
I always kind of felt
like a third wheel.
I'm sorry you felt that way.
No. No.
It must have been horrible.
Then again, I've...
made so many mistakes in my life.
Maybe... maybe I'm the
one who needs fixing.
You're a brilliant scientist
who runs the most
successful lab on the planet.
I don't think you need fixing.
'Cause from where I'm standing,
you're a pretty awesome human being.
One I'd like to get
to know a lot better.
I'd like that too.
♪ ♪
What is taking so long?
Uh, federal agents
will be here any minute
to take you into custody.
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Officer. Mr. Carver.
When your paperwork came across my desk,
I thought a VIP such as yourself
shouldn't have to ride in
a two-bit government van.
So I'm here to escort you
personally into custody.
Allen, a word?
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let me walk out of here with Carver,
and Mother will give you Iris.
[SCOFFS]
Eva is not interesting
in a fight with you
or with your friends.
You knew we were in that warehouse
when you set it on fire.
That feels like a fight to me.
Let me have him, Barry.
He's a bad man.
Bring Iris home.
Get your life back.
Are we doing this or what?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- [GRUNTS]
- On my six!
What the hell?
[FLASH]
Will someone please tell me
what the hell is going on?
I saved you. That's what's going on.
- Nash.
- What?
♪ ♪
The Barry Allen I know
would never, never have
considered that deal.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[MIRROR CRACKLING]
I knew Eva was ambitious,
but Mirror Duplicates.
Eva's more powerful than you thought.
I don't get it.
Why doesn't she just
come after you herself?
Well, Eva's still technically missing,
so she can't be seen in public.
That's why she took Singh.
The chief of police
could get close to you.
[SIGHS]
Fortunately, Mr. Wells
teleported us to safety.
You're welcome.
What is that device?
And how much do you want for it?
It's not for sale, dirtbag.
[LAUGHS] Oh, please.
Everyone has a price.
Hey, listen. We just saved your keister.
So why don't you put a sock in it
till we can figure out
what to do with you?
So guess we're stuck with
our new guest for a while.
It's only a matter of time
before Eva shows up here.
Right. Any mirrored surface
inside S.T.A.R. labs
is a door for her to walk through.
McCulloch security
system can protect us.
I have a panic room
Eva doesn't know about.
No offense, but extra
guards and a locked den
aren't gonna help us out here.
I have a biogenic ionization field
that can be activated
around the entire facility.
Anything breaking in would
be atomized in a second.
We just have to get there.
We could take the sewer system.
Pop over underneath R and D?
I break into things.
Mm.
No time like the present?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Allen.
I wanna ask you a question.
You knew that Carver was
in mortal danger, right,
as soon as Mirror-Singh
stepped off that elevator.
Why didn't you get him out of there?
I couldn't exactly run him
out of there as Barry Allen.
Or he offered you a deal.
That's the other thing.
I have all these Wells in
my head, and they all...
they're all screaming the same thing,
that the Barry Allen they knew
would never have hesitated.
You did.
You were considering the deal.
You were considering trading
Carver's life to save Iris.
It's more complicated than that.
- It's more complicated...
- Yeah.
Is it complicated like
in the way you almost
killed Eobard Thawne
and me along with him?
- No. That was different.
- How is that different?
Iris is my wife.
I have to save her.
How do you not understand that?
I do.
But what do you think Iris will say
when you tell her
you traded another
person's life to save hers?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[BEEPING]
[DOOR MECHANICALLY UNLOCKING]
[LIGHTS WHOOSHING]
A.R.G.U.S. will be here in an
hour to take you into custody.
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Wait, this isn't safe.
- Relax.
After I saw what happened to your wife,
I had it coated with protective nanites.
I thought Palmer Tech
and McCulloch were rivals.
[SCOFFS]
Let's just say what Palmer Tech
doesn't know won't hurt them.
[BEEPS]
And this is my panic room.
Concrete walls and
not a mirror in sight.
Even if my outer field
fails, Eva can't get in here.
Well, once the building's clear,
you can engage your ion field.
[KEYS CLACKING]
Then tell your people to
speed up the evacuation.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
Allegra, here. Take this.
Just in case. All right?
Any trouble, you should blast it
with one of your UV Rays.
All right? Provide a
welcome distraction.
When are you gonna stop trying?
Never.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What the hell?
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
[SCOFFS] I knew you were lying.
You really can't take a hint.
You're not here to rob the place.
And Carver didn't have a
change of heart on your parents.
You... you offered to take
their place in Black Hole.
Carver agrees.
I'm more valuable than my parents.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Sue, you...
you don't have to do this.
Yes, I do. I've been trying to collect
leverage on Carver for over a year.
He's untouchable.
Untouchable unless you have one of those
handy-dandy Black Hole pins.
You joined Black Hole
to get close to Carver.
Because you're gonna kill him.
That's why you're here, isn't it?
Carver's never gonna let my parents go.
Sue, damn it...
- It's the only way it ends.
- You gotta listen to me.
There... there is always another way.
Do you understand what
happens if you kill Carver?
Every time you look in the mirror,
you won't recognize
the person looking back.
- You'll lose yourself.
- Why do you care?
Because I believe in you!
And I know there's still good in you.
I can see it.
I'm sorry about this, slick.
[SPRAYS BREATH SPRAY]
[SNIFFING ERRATICALLY]
Oh, come on.
[THUDS]
All clear down here.
Ready for the force field when you are.
[COMPUTER BEEPS, ACTIVATES]
The ion field's up and running.
Now all that's left
to do is sit and wait.
Cheers.
[COUGHING]
[LIGHTS CLICK OFF, POWER SHUTS DOWN]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[SIGHS] That's not good.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Guys, the force field
isn't working anymore.
Can we find out what
happened to the power source?
We know what happened.
♪ ♪
Carver's angels invited
themselves to the party.
[BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
Something Carver never did.
We're no longer under his thumb.
Neither is Eva.
Whatever she is paying
you, I will double it.
This isn't about a paycheck.
It's about payback.
[PHOTON RIFLE ACTIVATES]
Eva's coming for you, Carver.
And we're gonna make sure
no one gets in her way.
♪ ♪
[ALL GRUNTING]
[PHOTON RIFLE BLASTING, LIGHTS SPARK]
[GRUNTS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Nice family reunion!
[FIGHTING PLAYING OVER TV MONITOR]
Eva's gonna be here any minute.
We have to get your ion field back up.
Is there an alternate power source?
The sub-basement.
There's remote access
to a secondary generator.
Guys, hold them off as long as you can.
I'm gonna get the power back on.
You do that. I know
how to handle traitors.
[PHONE BEEPING]
[PHOTON RIFLE BLASTING, LIGHTS SPARKING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Drop your weapons!
♪ ♪
Singh.
You don't wanna do this.
This isn't your will.
Eva's will is my will.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[LASER CANON BLASTS]
[THUDS]
♪ ♪
Success is assured.
[DYNAMIC MUSIC]
[ALL GRUNTING]
♪ ♪
[MEN SCREAMING]
[PHOTON RIFLE BLASTING, LIGHTS SPARKING]
[ALL GRUNTING, SCREAMING]
♪ ♪
I thought Sunshine was solar-powered!
How the frak is she
frying people at night?
Those bracelets aren't fashion.
They're fuel.
They're solar energy battery packs.
Well, how do we get them off?
We just gotta increase
the internal temperature,
overload the cells. Allegra, if you...
- Already on it.
- She's good.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know.
I'm making it up as I go.
[PHOTON RIFLE BLASTING]
[PHOTON RIFLE BLASTS]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTING]
[SPEAKING SPANISH] _
_
[PHOTON RIFLE BLASTING, LIGHTS SPARKING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
_
Fine. Do it.
You think you're the only
one that feels that way?
The only one that feels alone?
Get in line!
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
[GRUNTS]
Okay.
Remember when I told you
if things go sideways, zap the stone?
- Yeah.
- I'd zap the stone.
[UV LIGHT BEAM BLASTS]
[DISTORTED SCREAMING]
[WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTS]
[PHONE RIFLE WHIRRING]
[GRUNTING]
You came back.
Couldn't let you have all the fun.
Fun must mean something
entirely different
when you're rich.
[ENERGETIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GRUNTS]
[FIGHTING PLAYING OVER TV MONITOR]
[TV SHUTS OFF]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Honey...
I'm home.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Guess somebody forgot
to spike the punch.
[EXHALES]
[MIRROR SHIMMERS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
Oh!
Let's talk about this.
[LASER CANNON ACTIVATES, WHIRRS]
[CHUCKLES]
About what?
How you weaponized my technology?
Extorted charitable donors?
Kidnapped and blackmailed
innocent meta-humans
like Kimiyo, Esperanza, and Millie?
This is me talking.
I did what I had to do.
[LASER CANNON DEACTIVATES]
[SIGHS]
Then I'll do what I have to do.
Good-bye, Joseph.
[MIRRORS SHIMMER]
No, Eva! Wait!
- [GRUNTS]
- [YELPS]
No!
What don't you understand?
He's not worth saving!
[STRAINED] Maybe...
But it's not your decision.
Oh, yes, it is.
[SCREAMS]
[COUGHS]
My husband...
let me rot in that world
for years!
He does not get to live
- in this one.
- [GRUNTING]
You're not my wife.
[CHOKING]
My wife died
in the particle accelerator explosion.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Well...
I've never felt more alive.
You're not...
even....
human.
No. No.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
[GROANS]
Ahh!
God!
[LABORED BREATHING]
What are you doing here?
I'm making this up as I go.
Right.
Flash. Barry.
You and I are not enemies.
- We never have been.
- [GROANS]
You just killed him in cold blood.
Your wife
set out to catch a bad man.
She couldn't.
But together, we could.
- We're on the same side.
- No.
Just remember that.
All right, on three, everybody go crazy.
Got it.
That seems like bad advice.
Song title. No, I like it.
It'll be good. All right.
One, two...
Stand down.
Joseph is dead.
Well...
I didn't see that coming.
You're gonna let us go?
Of course.
I've achieved my goal for today.
We'll never stop coming after you.
[LABORED BREATHING]
You'll fail.
This building, this company...
It's all mine.
[GROANS]
And you and your little
friends are trespassing, so...
run along now, Barry,
before I have to call the police.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Mrs. McCulloch, where have
you been all this time?
Well, over the past six years,
I have been held hostage
by an international crime syndicate.
Forced to watch
as they stole my technology
and used it to create deadly weapons.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
How did you escape?
My husband, Joseph.
He worked tirelessly to try to find me.
And, um, he succeeded...
only to be murdered moments
after we were reunited.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Words cannot express my sorrow.
But know that I am working with the CCPD
to try to find my husband's murderer.
And as for McCulloch Technologies,
I will be resuming my position as CEO,
effective immediately.
It's what Joseph would have wanted.
Thank you.
[KNOCKING]
Going somewhere?
Carver's dead,
which means my parents are finally free.
And so am I.
I'm going home.
Sue, I'm not sure you can.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC]
Eva framed you...
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
For Carver's murder.
_
Barry, we've been through
stuff like this before.
Don't worry.
You're gonna find a way to stop Eva
and get Iris back.
I can't even be frustrated without...
[SIGHS] Without losing more of it.
[SIGHS]
Maybe instead of focusing
on what you've lost,
you should try remembering
what you'll never lose.
The reason you've beat
Zoom, Godspeed, Thawne?
It's because speed
isn't what drives you.
It's love.
That's your true force,
and there is nothing
artificial about that.
So as long as you stay true to yourself,
you will always find a
way to beat the bad guys.
And gals.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC]
I'm gonna miss you.
I'll be back before you know it.
[DOOR OPENS]
All set?
Car's downstairs.
I promise I'll get these
two back to you and your team
as soon as possible.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, um...
Frost can hear me, too, right?
As long as she's awake.
I'm awake. Really.
Go ahead.
Just get better.
And hurry back.
We still have a whitewater
rafting trip to take.
I'm holding you to that.
She says she can't wait.
♪ ♪
Tell the team I miss them already?
I will.
♪ ♪
Well, well.
- This is a little quieter.
- Yeah.
Hey, look. I know that I'm...
not your favorite person,
but if ever you need anything,
if you ever need my coffee.
What... what happened
to, "I don't like coffee"?
[LAUGHING]
Okay.
- Thanks.
- For what?
For this.
Of course.
What did it do to her? My cousin?
It made her relive her worst memory.
You know what?
You hang on to it.
Just in case you need it again.
Hey, guys.
- Hey.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
- Iris and the others,
they're still Eva's prisoners.
We're gonna get them back.
And remember, we still have
one thing that Eva doesn't.
Hope.
We also have reinforcements.
[TRIUMPHANT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- Oh.
- Joe.
♪ ♪
How are you here?
Well, it turns out that
when the guy that's trying
to kill you kicks the bucket,
they lift the protection detail.
- That makes sense.
- Nash.
Hey, man. Yeah.
- Hey.
- And just in time.
Team needs you now more than ever.
Well, let's go save some people we love.
♪ ♪
You have been at this for hours.
Barry wouldn't give up.
And the woman that he
married wouldn't either.
I found him!
David's at Central City Hospital.
I can't believe I just did that.
Holy frak. Iris, you
can control this place.
Iris?
Iris, stay with me!
Iris!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --